Guide to the Edwin C. Taylor and Robert Galvin Drawings of Yale University Buildings
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Edwin C. Taylor and Robert Galvin drawings of Yale University buildings
1930-1941
RU 1020
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.75
The materials consist of 18 original ink drawings by Edwin C. Taylor and Robert Galvin of Yale dinnerware designs depicting Yale buildings.
Taylor, Edwin C.
Galvin, Robert, artist
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-A (YRG 46-A), Records and materials broadly documenting Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by artist.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of 18 original ink drawings by Edwin C. Taylor and Robert Galvin of Yale dinnerware designs depicting Yale buildings.
Tableware -- Design; Drawings (visual works); Galvin, Robert, artist; Taylor, Edwin C.; Yale University -- Buildings
- Drawings, 1930-1941; Series I
  - Taylor, Edwin C.
    - First Yale College, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut Hall, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Old Chapel, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Old Library, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - South Sheffield Hall, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Yale College Fence and Campus, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Wrexham Tower, Memorial Quadrangle, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Harkness Memorial Tower, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Sheffield-Vanderbilt Hall, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Walter Camp Memorial Gateway, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Bridge of the School of the Fine Arts, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Entrance to Sterling Memorial Library, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Galvin, Robert
    - [Divinity School?], 1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Berkeley College, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jonathan Edwards College, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Pierson College, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Davenport College, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Timothy Dwight College, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)